gamingph.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy – GamingPH.com

Here on GamingPH.com (“Company”, “GamingPH”, “Gaming.PH”, “GamingPH.com”, “We” or “Us”) we take care data privacy seriously. This privacy policy page is made to demonstrate how we collection information

**What information do we collect from visitors?**

We only collect anonymous information that does not identify visitors identity such as browser information, time/duration of visits and geo-location (country, city), this information are use from our third-party services like Google Analytics and Google AdSense.

We don’t collect any user personal information from users when visiting our site, except when you register for our newsletter (email address), or you join one of our giveaways (usually the data that we collected are name and email address).

**Do GamingPH.com uses Cookies?**

Yes, some of our third party application like Google Analytics uses cookies to determine site performance. For more information, please check our [Cookies Policy](https://gamingph.com/cookies-policy/) page.

**Do GamingPH.com disclose any personal  information from user to outside parties?**

Nope! We do not collect personal information when you visit our site.

**Third Party Website**

We may include third party products or services on our site like ads, recommended post and site analytics. In this case, we have no control over their policy. Some of the third party we are using are Google Adsense, Google Analytics, Anonymous Ads and Facebook Widgets.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We comply with the requirements of Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and we do not collection any personal information for anyone under 13 years old. Our website is intended for people who are at least 13 years of old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using or visiting our site, you agree or consent to our website privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decided to change our privacy policy, we will update this post and marked the date of the changes. This privacy policy was last modified on February, 2017.

**Contacting Us**

You may reach us via [contact@gamingph.com](mailto:contact@gamingph.com).
